American Philosophical Society Archives. Record Group IIh. 1892-1896 APS.Archives.IIh APS.Archives.IIh
American Philosophical Society
- Papers
  - Letter to [Henry] Phillips, April 27, 1894; 9x5-3/4; Mercantile Library of Philadelphia
    Phila., A.L.S.: John Edmands, Libn. 1p., end. Asks price of various issues of Proceedings.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, April 28, 1894; 10-3/4x8-1/2; Frazer, Persifor, 1844-1909
    Phila., Typed L.S. 1p., end. Asks to copy plate of Washington signatures used in his paper, "Composite photography applied to handwriting." For printed paper, see: APS Proceedings vol. 23, pp. 433-441.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, April 28, 1894; 7x4-1/2; Ganguli, Sanjibau
    Jeypore, India, A.L.S. 2p. Asks to be elected to the A.P.S.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, April 28, 1894; 11x8-1/2; Rhode Island Historical Society
    Providence, R.I., A.L.S.: Amos Perry 1p., end. Offers to return duplicates of APS publications. Many from library of J.R. Bartlett.
  - Letter to John [sic] Phillips, April 29, 1894; 9-1/4x5-1/2; Scudder, Samuel Hubbard, 1837-1911
    Cambridge, [Mass.], A.L.S. 1p. Thanks for large number of copies of his paper on tertiary Tipulidae. For printed paper, see: APS Proceedings vol. 32, pp. 163-245.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, April 30, 1894; 8x5; Peter, Benjamin D.
    Lexington, Ky., A.L.S. 1p. Announces death of Robert Peter.
  - Letter to H[enry] Phillips, May 1, 1894; 8-1/4x5; Parry, Francis
    New York, A.L.S. 1p., end. Asks for copy of Brinton's paper on Nagualism.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, May 2, 1894; 12-3/4x8; Counsel, Edward
    Melbourne, Australia, A.L.S. 2p., end. Concerns his book of maxims, presented to the A.P.S.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, May 2, 1894; 11x8-1/4; Field, Robert Patterson, -1931
    Phila., Typed L.S. 1p., end. Change of address.
  - Letter to [Ella M] Morrison [sic, May 3, 1894; 7x4-1/2; Baird, Henry Carey, 1825-1912
    Phila., A.L.S. 2p. Concerns Ord portrait and his letter of presentation.
  - Letter to Henry Phillips, May 3, 1894; 11x8-1/2; Netherlands, Consul. New York
    New York, L.S.: J.R. Planten, Consul General. 1p., end. Cannot supply more copies of Flora Batava.
  - Letter to [Frederick Fraley], May 4, 1894; 11x8; Baird, Henry Carey, 1825-1912
    Phila., Typed L.S. with MS. Corrections 3p. Presents Portrait of George Ord, Copied by T.H. Smith from Nagle Portrait at the Academy of natural sciences. Appends list of subscribers.
  - Letter to F[rederick] Fraley, Phila., May 8, 1894; 8-1/4x5-1/4; Phillips, Henry, 1838-1895
    Lucerne, A.L.S. 4p. Reports on travels and state of his health.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, May 10, 1894; 10x8; Lyman, Benjamin Smith, 1835-1920
    Phila., A.L.S. 1p. Will read paper on "Some New Red Horizons" at next meeting. For printed paper, see: APS Proceedings vol. 33, pp. 192-215.
  - Letter to [Henry] Phillips, May 10, 1894; 8x5-1/2; Scott, William Berryman, 1858-1947
    Princeton, N.J., A.L.S. 1p. About shipment of plates from Werner & Winter.
  - Letter to [Ella M] Morrison [sic; Phila.], May 10, [1894]; 3-1/2x5-1/2; Brinton, Daniel Garrison, 1837-1899
    A.L.S. on postal card 1p. and add. Will be absent tomorrow evening.
  - Letter to Ella [M] Morrison [sic], May 11, 1894; 8x5; Price, John Sergeant, 1831-1897
    Phila., A.L.S. 1p., end. Concerns minutes of last meeting. Inquires about Wanamaker's bill.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, May 14, 1894; 3-1/2x5-1/2; Thorn, F. M.
    Orchard Park, N.Y., A.L.S. on postal card 1p., end. and add. Asks for copy of flatest issue of the Transactions.
  - Letter to [Henry Phillips], May 17, 1894; 8-1/4x5; Hyatt, Alpheus, 1838-1902
  - Letter to Ella [M] Morrison [sic], May 18, 1894; 8x5; Price, John Sergeant, 1831-1897
    Phila., A.L.S. 1p. Gives permission for A.P. Smith to take some measurements.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, May 19, 1894; 8x5; Fraley, F. (Frederick), 1804-1901
    [Phila.], L. 1p. Enc. wanting. Appoints Ruschenberger to prepare obituary of W.V. Keating. Encloses letter from Phillips. For enclosure, see Phillips to Fraley, May 8, 1894.
  - Letter to the [American philosophical society], May 19, [1894]; 8-1/4x5-1/4; Nadaillac, Jean-François-Albert du Pouget, marquis de, 1818-1904
    Paris, A.L.S. 2p., end. Sends list of books he would like to give to the A.P.S.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, May 20, 1894; 3-1/2x5-1/2; McVey, John Joseph
    Phila., L. on postal card 1p., end., and add. Quotes copy of first edition of APS Transactions.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, May 21, 1894; 9-1/2x6; Borgmann, Emil, b. 1874
    St. Louis, Mo., A.L.S. 1p., end. Wants to obtain issues of the Proceedings.
  - Letter to [Ella M] Morison, May 21, 1894; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Patterson, Christopher Stuart, 1842-1924
    Phila., A.L.S. 1p., end. Asks for copy of report on Sesquicentennial Celebration.
  - Letter to [Henry] Phillips, May 21, 1894; 10x8; Rogers, Robert William, 1864-1930
    Madison, N.J., Typed L.S. 1p., end. Asks for credentials as delegate to the Congrès international des orientalistes.
  - Receipt for manuscript by Cope, Scott and A.P. Brown, May 22, 1894; 9x5-3/4; MacCalla & co.
    Phila., D. 1p.
  - Letter to the [American philosophical society], May 22, 1894; 9x5-1/2; Partridge, D. Anson
    Phila., A.L.S. 1p., end. Gives estimate on lithographing maps for Lyman's paper on red horizons. For paper, see: APS Proceedings, vol.33, pp. 192-215.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, May 23, 1894; 9-1/4x5-3/4; Frazer, Persifor, 1844-1909
    Phila., A.L.S. 1p. Enc. wanting. Sends text of his remarks at last meeting, on new red horizons. See: APS Proceedings, vol. 33, p. 259.
  - Receipt for B.S. Lyman's "Some new red horizons", May 25, 1894; 9x5-3/4; MacCalla & co.
  - Letter to Henry Phillips, May 26, 1894; 10x7-3/4; Cresson, Hilborne Thomson
    Phila., A.L.S. 3p. Gives his interpretation of a part of the Troano manuscript. Refers to the Dresden Codex, Dr. Förstemann, D.G. Brinton.
  - Letter to H[enry] Phillips, May 26, 1894; 3-1/4x5-1/4; Kegan Paul, Trench, Trübner & Co., Ltd.
    London, L. on postal card 1p., end., and add. Inquires about an order for Transactions.
  - Letter to H[enry] Phillips, May 26, 1894; 3-1/4x5-1/4; Kegan Paul, Trench, Trübner & Co., Ltd.
    London, L. on postal card 1p., and add. Orders copy of Transactions.
  - Receipt for manuscripts by Persifor Frazer, May 28, 1894; 9x5-3/4; MacCalla & co.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, May 31, [1894]; 3-1/2x5-1/2; Brinton, Daniel Garrison, 1837-1899
    Media, Pa., A.L.S. on postal card 1p., end: Dr. Horn attended to Dr. Cresson's letter, and add. Concerns Cresson's letter.
  - Letter to Henry Phillips; Boyden P.O., N.C., June 6, 1894; 3-1/2x5-1/2; Sharswood, William, 1835- (?)
    A.L.S. on postal card 1p., end. and add. Asks about biographical notice of George Sharswood.
  - Letter to H[enry] Phillips, June 16, 1894; 3-1/4x5-1/4; Kegan Paul, Trench, Trübner & Co., Ltd.
    London, L. on postal card 1p. and add. Inquires about order for Transactions.
  - Letter to Henry N[iving] Ogden, June 18, 1894; 9x5-3/4; Morison, Ella M.
    Phila., A.L.S. 1p. Draft. Offers bound copy of Transactions, vol. 6, o.s., containing requested copy of Dunbar's Description of the Mississippi delta.
  - Letter to [Henry Phillips], June 18, 1894; 7x4-1/2; Nadaillac, Jean-François-Albert du Pouget, marquis de, 1818-1904
    Paris, A.L.S. 3p. end. Has sent books listed.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, June 22, 1894; 3-1/2x5-1/2; G.E. Stechert & Co.
    New York, Printed L. filled in in MS. 1p., end., and add. Asks price of sets of publications.
  - Letter to [Kegan Paul, Trench, Trübner & co., Ltd, June 26, 1894; 9-3/4x8-1/2; Morison, Ella M.
    Phila.], L. 1p. Copy. Concerns order for Transactions.
  - Letter to Henry Phillips, June 27, 1894; 9-1/4x5-3/4; Gutekunst, Frederick, 1831-1917
    Phila., A.L.S. 1p., end. Has portrait or Fraley for sale.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, June, [1894]; 11-3/4x9-1/4; Ogden, Henry Vining, 1857-1931
    Milwaukee, Wis., A.L.S. 1p., end. Requests copy of Dunbar's Description of the delta of the Mississippi, in A.P.S. Transactions, vol. 6, o.s., pp. 165-187.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, July 1, 1894; 7x4-1/2; Roberts, Isaac, 1829-1904
    Sussex, A.L.S. 3p., end. Concerns corrections to be made in the paper he presented at the Sesquicentennial Celebration. For printed paper, see; APS Proceedings vol. 32, pp. 97-104.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, July 3, 1894; 10-1/2x8; Keefe, John C.
    Milwaukee, A.L.S. 1p., end. Enc. Wanting. Asks for particulars about Phillips prize essay.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, July 7, 1894; 3-1/2x5-1/2; Boston Book Company
    Boston, Typed L. on postal card 1p., end., and add. Asks price of set of Proceedings.
  - Letter to [Ella M] Morrison [sic], July 11, 1894; 8x5; Price, John Sergeant, 1831-1897
    Phila., A.L.S. 1p. Will not pay bill for displaying flag at Hall on July 4th.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, July 11, 1894; 3-1/2x5-1/2; Schäfer und Koradi
    Phila., L. on postal card 1p., end., and add Asks price of McCauley's Dictionary of Egyptian Hieroglyphics. For printed paper, see: APS Transactions. vol. 16, pp. 1-241.
  - Letter to [John Sergeant] Price, July 12, 1894; 9x5-3/4; Morison, Ella M.
    Phila., A.L.S. 1p. Bill for display of flag on July 4th had been authorized by him, and should be paid.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, July 25, 1894; 3-1/2x5-1/2; Sener, Samuel Miller, 1855-1911
    Lancaster, Pa., A.L.S. on postal card 1p., end. and add. Asks for copy of Sesquicentennial report. He was delegate from Linnean Society of Lancaster.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, July 28, 1894; 8x5, 3-1/2x6-1/2; Green, William W.
    Oswego, [N.Y.], A.L.S. 2p., end. Enc. Asks for particulars on Phillips prize essay. Encloses self-addressed envelope.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, Aug. 3, 1894; 8x4-3/4; Barnard, Edith S.
    Mt. Airy, Md., A.L.S. 2p. Enc. wanting. Announces death of her father, William T. Barnard.
  - Letter to [Henry] Phillips, Aug. 10, 1894; 5-1/2x4-1/4; Gregory, Henry Duval, 1819-1897
    Montreal A.L.S. 1p. Remarks of J.S. Price's health.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, Aug. 10, 1894; 7x8-1/2; Harley, Lewis R. (Lewis Reifsneider), b. 1866
    North Wales, Pa., A.L.S. 1p. Asks for particulars about Phillips prize essay.
  - Letter to Henry Philips [sic], Aug. 22, 1894; 5-1/4x8; Williams, Talcott, 1849-1928
    Phila., Typed L.S. 1p. Concerns Library's holdings of transactions of Straits branch of Royal Asiatic Society.
  - Letter to [Henry Phillips], Sept. 7, 1894; 6-3/4x5-3/4; Theodore L. De Vinne & Co.
    New York. L, 1p., end., and end. Inquires about various editions of Poor Richard's Almanack.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, Sept. 10, 1894; 9-1/2x6; American Book Company
    New York, L. 1p. and end. Asks for copy of Rothrock's "Forests of Pennsylvania." For printed paper, see: APS Proceedings vol. 33, pp. 114-133.
  - Letter to Henry M. Philips [sic], Sept. 10, 1894; 8x5; Rothermel, Peter Frederick, 1812-1895
    A.L.S. 1p. Enc. wanting. Sends something.
  - Letter to Henry Phillips, Sept. 13, 1894; 10-1/2x8; Williams, Talcott, 1849-1928
    Phila., Typed L.S. 1p. and end. Concerns transactions of the Straits branch of the Royal Asiatic Society.
  - Letter to Henry Phillips, Sept. 14, 1894; 11x8-1/2; Popular science monthly
    New York, A.L.S.: Frederick A. Fernald 1p., end. Concerns biographical sketches of Rittenhouse, Robert Hare.
  - Letter to Henry Phillips, Sept. 18, 1894; 5-1/4x8; Williams, Talcott, 1849-1928
    Phila., Typed L.S. 1p. Concerns transactions of the Straits Branch of the Royal Asiatic Society.
  - Letter to Henry Phillips, Sept. 19, 1894; 9x5-3/4; Genth, F. A. (Frederick Augustus), 1855?-1910
    Phila., A.L.S. 1p. Gives mailing address.
  - Letter to Henry Phillips, Sept. 24, 1894; 8x5; Fraley, F. (Frederick), 1804-1901
    [Phila.], L. 1p., end. Appoints Ryder, Chapman and Sharp as committee on Cope's paper on taxonomy of Ophidia. For printed paper, see: APS Transactions, vol. 18, pp. 186-219.
  - Letter to [Henry Phillips], Sept. 26, 1894; 7x4-1/2; Boudinot, J. J. (Jane J.)
    Bernardville, N.J., A.L.S. 2p., end. Inquiry about Silas Deane and Arthur Lee letters.
  - Letter to [Henry] Phillips, Sept. 27, 1894; 8x5; Price, Eli Kirk, d. 1933
    Phila., A.L.S. 1p., end. Gives total amount spent on publications, 1893 to date.
  - Letter to Frederick Fraley, Sept. 28, 1894; 11x8-1/2; Parker, Leroy, 1844-1926
    Buffalo, N.Y., Typed L.S. 1p., end. Asks for particulars on Phillips prize essay.
  - Letter to T. Guilford Smith, Buffalo, N.Y., Sept. 28, 1894; 10x8; State University of New York. Regents office
    Albany, N.Y., Typed L. 1p. Concerns law schools in N.Y. state. Refers to Phillips prize essay.
  - Letter to Henry Phillips, Sept. 29, 1894; 3-1/2x5-1/2; Nadaillac, Jean-François-Albert du Pouget, marquis de, 1818-1904
    Rougemont, [France], A.L.S. on postal card 1p., end., and add., end. Inquires about his shipment of books.
  - Letter to H.C. Phillips [sic], Sept. 29, 1894; 10x8; State University of New York.
    Buffalo, N.Y., Typed L.S.: T. Guilford Smith. 1p. Enc. wanting. Sends letter from Regents office at Albany. Concerns Phillips prize circulars. For enclosure, see State univ. of N.Y. Regents office to T.G. Smith, Sept. 28, 1894.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, Sept. 30, 1894; 7x4-1/2; Spencer, Harned Eldridge
    Tarrytown, N.Y., A.L.S. 3p., end. Asks about MS. genealogy of Pocahontas which he believes to be in APS collections.
  - Letter to the [American philosophical society], [Sept.], 1894; 10x8; Borovka, N.
    Odessa, Russia, A.L.S. 2p., end. In French. Asks for correspondence on the question of forming a universal language.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, Oct. 1, 1894; 10-1/2x8; Carleton, Mark Alfred, 1866-1925
    Washington, A.L.S. 1p., end., and end. Asks about Schweinitz's Synopsis fungorum in America Boreali media degentium.
  - Receipt to A[lbert] E. Foote for payment for Transactions, Oct. 5, 1894; 3-3/4x7, 3x8-3/4; American Philosophical Society
    Phila., Printed D. filled in in MS., S.: H[enry] Phillips. 1p. Enc. of Phillips' MS. note of coming publications
  - Letter to Henry Phillips, Oct. 5, 1894; 3-1/2x5-1/4; Borovko, G.
    Odessa, A.L.S. on postal card 1p. and add. In Esperanto
  - Note, Oct. 5, 1894; 7x4-1/2; Robins, James W.
    [Phila.], A.N. in 3d person 1p., end. Gives address.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, Oct. 8, 1894; 8x5-1/4; Library Company of Philadelphia
    Phila., A.L.S.: Geo[rge] Maurice Abbot. 1p., end. Exchange of publications.
  - Letter to Henry Phillips, Oct. 8, 1894; 10x8; State University of New York.
    Buffalo, N.Y. Typed L.S.: T. Guilford Smith. 1p. will sent out Phillips prize circulars. Refers to circular on international language.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, Oct. 9, 1894; 3-1/2x5-1/2; Miller, Gerrit S. (Gerrit Smith), 1869-1956
    Peterboro, N.Y., A.L.S. on postal card 1p., end. and add. Asks for certain issue of the Proceedings, 1871.
  - Letter to the [American philosophical society], Oct. 11, 1894; 9-1/2x6; Todd, David P. (David Peck), 1855-1939
    Amherst, Mass., L.S. 1p., and end. Asks to borrow plates used for Isaac Roberts' paper on astronomical progress, in A.P.S. Proceedings, vol. 32, pp. 97-104
  - Letter to the [American philosophical society;:, Oct. 12, 1894; 9x5-3/4; Kaiserlich-Königliche Zoologisch-Botanische Gesellschaft in Wien
    Vienna, A.L.S.: Hahlbruckner 1p., end. In German. Exchange of publications.
  - Letter to Henry Phillips, Oct. 16, 1894; 10-1/2x8; James, Edmund J. (Edmund Janes), 1855-1925
    Phila., Typed L.S. 1p. Enc. wanting. Sends letter and asks about reply.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, Oct. 18, 1894; 5-3/4x7-3/4; Joseph G. Taite's Sons
    Phila., Typed L. 1p. Sends estimate for weatherstripping windows in A.P.S. Hall.
  - Letter to [Frederick Fraley], Oct. 18, 1894; 10-3/4x8-1/2, 10-3/4x8-1/4; Revelli, Paolo, 1871-1956
    Turin, A.L.S. 1p. Printed enc. pasted to letter. In French. Sends announcement of celebration of 25th anniversary of Guido Cora's first publication in geography.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, Oct. 18, 1894; 5x8; State University of New York. Regents office
    Albany, N.Y., Typed L. 1p. Asks for copies of Phillips prize circulars, some to be sent to Seth Low and Austin Abbott.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, Oct. 20, 1894; 9-1/2x5-3/4; Frazer, Persifor, 1844-1909
    Phila., Typed L.S. 1p. Transmits two copies of "Gites Mineraux" at request of French consul.
  - Letter to [Henry] Phillips, Oct. 21, 1894; 9x5-3/4; Coues, Elliott, 1842-1899
    Washington, A.L.S. 1p. Asks about works of J.K. Townsend. Refers to Audubon, Academy of natural sciences.
  - Letter to Henry Phillips, Oct. 23, [1894]; 3-1/2x5-1/2; Nadaillac, Jean-François-Albert du Pouget, marquis de, 1818-1904
    Rougemont, [France], A.L.S. on postal card 1p., end., and add. Concerns his shipment of books. Will send in paper on Mashonaland.
  - Letter to [Frederick] Fraley, Oct. 24, 1894; 9-1/2x5-1/2; Frazer, Persifor, 1844-1909
    Phila., A.L.S. 1p. Will prepare obituary of E.Y. McCauley.
  - Receipt for Proceedings, No. 142, 144, Oct. 25, 1894; 2-3/4x5; Suess, Eduard, 1831-1914
    Vienna, D.S. with MS. additions 1p., end. Refers to B.S. Lyman.
  - Letter to Fred[eric]k Fraley, Oct. 26, 1894; 3-1/2x5-1/2; Bullowa, Ferdinand Ezra M.
    New York, A.L.S. on postal card 1p. and add. Asks for particulars about Phillips prize essay.
  - Letter to Henry Phillips, Oct. 26, 1894; 8x5; Fraley, F. (Frederick), 1804-1901
    [Phila.], L. 2p. Concerns amending of APS Laws. Frazer will prepare obituary of E.Y. Mccauley. Refers to Treasurer's illness.
  - Letter to [Henry] Phillips, Oct. 27, 1894; 11x8, 3-1/2x4; Stokes, Alfred C.
    Trenton, N.J., Typed L.S. 1p. Enc. Sends sample drawing for paper on Infusoria. Refers humorously to his work on apples. For printed paper on Infusoria, see: A.P.S. Proceedings, vol. 33, pp. 338-345.
  - Letter to Frederic[k] Fraley, Oct. 29, 1894; 11-1/4x8-1/2; Boerman, C. M.
    Chicago, A.L.S. 1p., end. Asks for particulars about Phillips prize essay.
  - Letter to Henry Phillips, Oct. 31, 1894; 9-1/2x6; Ingham, William A. (William Armstrong), 1827-1913
    Phila., A.L.S. 1p. Concerns weatherstripping of windows in A.P.S. Hall.
  - Letter to Henry Phillips, Nov. 8, 1894; 11x8-1/2; Popular science monthly
    New York, A.L.S.: Frederik A. Fernald. 2p. Concerns biographical sketches of S.C. Walker, Rittenhouse, Robert Hare. Refers to E.O. Kendall.
  - Letter to Henry Phillips, Nov. 9, 1894; 6-3/4x4-1/2; Wagner, Samuel, 1842-
    [Phila.], A.L.S. 1p. Cannot attend Council meeting.
  - Notice of consignment for A.P.S., Nov. 10, 1894; 3-1/2x5-1/2; Adams Express Company
    Phila., Printed L. filled in in MS. on postal card 1p., end., and add.
  - Letter to the American philosophical society, Nov. 10, 1894; 10-3/4x8-1/2; Clow, James Gillespie
    Mexico [City], A.L.S. 1p., end. Asks for copy of Haupt's paper on "The physical phenomena of harbor entrances," in APS Proceedings, vol. 25, pp. 19-41.
  - Letter to Henry Phillips, Nov. 15, 1894; 9-1/2x6; Ingham, William A. (William Armstrong), 1827-1913
    Phila., A.L.S. 1p. Enc. wanting. Returns bill sent for weatherstripping windows in Hall.
  - Letter to [William Armstrong Ingham; Phila.], Nov. 16, 1894; 4-1/2x8-1/4; Morison, Ella M.
    A.L.S. 1p. Enc. wanting. Sends letter concerning weatherstripping the windows in A.P.S. Hall.
  - Letter to Henry Phillips, Nov. 19, 1894; 9-1/2x6, 3-3/4x6-1/2; Ingham, William A. (William Armstrong), 1827-1913
    Phila., A.L.S. 1p., and add., end. Enc. wanting. Sends bill for repair to roof of APS Hall, which has come to him by mistake.
  - Subscription form for collations to follow stated meetings of the Society, Nov. 20, 1894; 8-3/4x5-1/2; American Philosophical Society
    Phila., Printed D. 7 copies variously signed: I.J. Wistar, J.E. Rhoads, J.T. Rothrock, C.N.Peirce, W.A. Ingham, C.B. Bullock, S. Castner.
  - Letter to Henry Phillips, Nov. 20, 1894; 8x5; Fraley, F. (Frederick), 1804-1901
    [Phila.], L.S. 1p., end. Appoints Brinton, Prime, Morehouse, W.H. Greene, Cattell to committee to consider Brinton's motion on amending election rules of A.P.S. See: APS Proceedings, vol. 32, pp. 369-370.
  - Subscription for collations, Nov. 20, 1894; 9x5-3/4; Phillips, Henry, 1838-1895
    Phila., A.D.S. 1p.
  - Letter to Henry Phillips, Nov. 20, 1894; 3-1/2x5-1/2; Stokes, Alfred C.
    Trenton, N.J., Typed L. on postal card 1p. and add. Concerns his paper on Infusoria. For printed paper, see: APS Proceedings vol. 33, pp. 338-345.
  - Letter to W[illiam] H[ouston] Greene, Nov. 21, 1894; 6-3/4x4-1/4; Clark, Clarence H. (Clarence Howard), 1833-1906
    [Phila.], A.L.S. 1p. Enc. wanting. Sends check for subscription to collations.
  - Letter to Henry Phillips, Nov. 21, 1894; 11x8, 3-1/2x6-1/4; Houston, Edwin J. (Edwin James), 1847-1914
    Phila., Typed L. 1p. and add., end. Enc. wanting. Sends letter from a Mr. Goodfellow.
  - Letter to W[illia]m H[ouston] Greene, Nov. 22, 1894; 7x4-1/2; Brinton, Daniel Garrison, 1837-1899
    Phila., A.L.S. 1p. Enc.wanting. Sends check for subscription to the collations.
  - Letter to W[illiam] H[ouston] Greene, Nov. 22, 1894; 8x5; Fraley, F. (Frederick), 1804-1901
    [Phila.], L. 1p. Enc. wanting. Sends check for subscription to collations.
  - Letter to William H[ouston] Green[e], Nov. 22, 1894; 11x8; Houston, Edwin J. (Edwin James), 1847-1914
    Phila., Typed L. 1p. Enc. wanting. Sends subscription for collations.
  - Letter to William H[ouston] Greene, Nov. 22, 1894; 9-1/2x6; D'Invilliers, E. V. (Edward Vincent), 1857-1928
    Phila., Typed L.S. 1p. Concerns subscription for collations.
  - Letter to [William Houston] Greene, Nov. 22, 1894; 5x8; Keen, William W. (William Williams), b. 1837
    Phila., Typed L.S. 1p. Enc. wanting. Sends check for subscription to collations.
  - Letter to W[illia]m H[ouston] Greene, Nov. 23, 1894; 9-1/2x5-1/2; Goodwin, Harold, 1850?-1935
    Phila., A.L.S. 1p. Concerns subscription for collations.
  - Letter to W[illia]m H[ouston] Greene, Nov. 23, 1894; 8x5; Price, John Sergeant, 1831-1897
    Phila., A.L.S. 1p. Enc. wanting. Sends Cadwalader Biddle's subscription to collations.
  - Letter to William Houston Greene, Nov. 23, 1894; Norris, Isaac
  - Letter to [William Houston] Greene, Nov. 23, 1894; 8-1/4x5; Rosengarten, J. G. (Joseph George), 1835-1921
    [Phila.], A.L.S. 1p. Enc. wanting. Sends subscription for collations.
  - Letter to [William Houston] Greene, Nov. 26, 1894; 8x5; Du Bois, Patterson, 1847-1917
    Phila., A.L.S. 1p., end. Enc. wanting. Sends check for subscription to collations.
  - Letter to W[illia]m H[ouston] Greene, Nov. 27, 1894; 10-3/4x8-1/4; Tatham, W. P. (William P.)
    Phila., A.L.S. 1p. Enc. wanting. Sends subscription for collations.
  - Letter to W[illiam] H[ouston] Greene, Nov. 27, 1894; 8x5; Tyson, James, 1841-1919
    Phila., A.L.S. 1p. Concerns subscription for collations. Professional duties prevent him from attending meetings.
  - Letter to [William] H[ouston] Greene, Nov. 28, 1894; 11x8-1/2; Dolley, Charles S.
    Phila., A.L.S. 1p. Approves of subscription for collations.
  - Letter to D[aniel] G[arrison] Brinton, Phila., Nov. 28, 1894; 11x8-1/2, 3x6-1/2; Douglass, Earl, b. 1862